Guide to the Vassar College Class Records, 1865-2021
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Class of 1898, [3.6 cubic feet (12 boxes)]
  - "Miss Fanny Borden,", undated (Box 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 4)
  - Notes on first informal reunion, 1950 (Box 7)
  - Notes on second informal reunion, 1952 (Box 7)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 3)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 12)
  - Photographs - Children of alumnae, undated (Box 3)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 4)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 7)
  - Printed ephemera, undated; [3 folders] (Box 12)
  - Proof sheets of 50th reunion bulletin (pg.1-91), 1948 (Box 4)
  - Reunion materials class of 1898, undated (Box 4)
  - Reunion notes, undated (Box 7)
  - Reunion notes, 1955 (Box 9)
  - Stamps, undated (Box 3)
  - "Take A Tete with 1898,", 1942 (Box 11)
  - Treasurer's book, undated (Box 2)
  - Vassar Class songs 1898, undated (Box 2)
  - VC Alumnae council, 1946-1950 (Box 9)
  - VC Alumnae council, 1950-1951 (Box 9)
  - VC Alumnae council, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
  - VC Alumnae council, 1952-1953 (Box 9)
- Class of 1899, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - "Keystone Memorandum book,", undated (Box 2)
  - 40th reunion materials class of 1899, 1939 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1899 official reports, 1922 (Box 2)
  - College ephemera, undated; [3 folders] (Box 2)
  - Collegiate primer, undated (Box 2)
  - Commencement and class day ephemera, 1899 (Box 1)
  - Comparison of Mt. Holyoke and Vassar in the 1950s, undated (Box 2)
  - Illustrated poem - "A Cycle from Omar Khayyam,", undated (Box 1)
  - Letters from the class representative, 1931, undated (Box 1)
  - Letters to Jean James Tawney, undated (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous stamps, undated (Box 2)
  - Pamphlet - "'99 Class Songs,", [1899?]; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "Class Day Book 1899,", [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "Looking Backward: A Farce in One Act,", 1924; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "Record of Ninety-Nine's Thirty-Fifth Reunion at Vassar,", 1934 Jul 8; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "Reunion Record of the Class of 1899,", 1909 Jun; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "Reunion Record of the Class of 1899,", 1920 Jun (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "Reunion Record of the Class of Ninety-Nine at Vassar College,", 1939 Jun; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "The Growth of Greatness,", 1896 Oct 31 (Box 1)
  - Pocketbook and ephemera from 75th Anniversary, belonging to Jean James (VC 1899), 1974 (Box 1)
  - Reunion ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Reunion materials class of 1899, undated; [3 folders] (Box 2)
  - Treasurer's account book (Julia Frances Wicker), 1904-1953 (Box 1)
- Class of 1900, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class day book and notebook, 1900 (Box 1)
  - Class day exercises, 1900 Jun 12 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1900 Mabel Schmidt letters and notices, undated (Box 1)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 1)
  - Excerpt from Vassarion, 1900 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated; [3 folders] (Box 1)
  - Program for "In the Reign of the Precedent,", undated (Box 1)
  - "Vassar World" Vol. XXXIV No.99, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1901, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - 1901 Sophomore joke book, 1899 (Box 2)
  - Alumni obituaries: Helen Swartz, Mabel Farnham Mangano, Margery Currey, Elsie La Grange Cole Phillips, Almeda Robbins, undated (Box 2)
  - Article - "A Pink House Museum,", undated (Box 2)
  - Article - "Class of 1901 returns to Vassar,", undated (Box 2)
  - Article - "Thirty-two-Year-Old Club Teaches Girls to Use Government, undated (Box 2)
  - Article on Julia Stimson, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1901 bulletin information, undated (Box 2)
  - Class day book, 1901; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Class Day exercises, 1901; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Class songs, 1901 (Box 2)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 1)
  - Envelope - "Misc Books" (Class day book, class songs, "Looking Backward," "The College Ladies Companion,", undated (Box 1)
  - Letter from Parker, Ruth Louise (VC 1901), undated (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous alumnae obituaries, undated (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, undated (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 2)
  - Notice for "The 50th Anniversary of the Opening of Vassar College,", undated (Box 2)
  - Notice for "The Anna Justice Fund,", undated; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Pamphlet and letter for "The Abbot E. Kitteridge Club for Girls, undated (Box 2)
  - Photographs of the class of 1901, undated (Box 1)
  - Plaque: "Stimson Library in memory of Julia Stimson,", undated (Box 2)
  - Poems from Helen Storke (VC 1901), undated (Box 2)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 2)
  - Program for "Charles C. Burleigh, Jr.: A Memorial Exhibition,", undated (Box 2)
  - Program for "Tree Ceremonies,", undated (Box 2)
  - Program for play - "The Vassar Adamant,", undated (Box 2)
  - Program for The Commencement Luncheon, undated (Box 2)
  - Record of physical measurements for Newdell, Elsie, undated (Box 2)
  - Reunion records - 29th, 30th, 5th, undated (Box 2)
  - Reunion song, undated (Box 2)
  - Script for play - "Mene Mene Tekel Upharsin,", undated; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Written accounts of 60th reunion of the class of 1901, 1961 (Box 1)
- Class of 1902, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - Articles on Wright, Maud (VC 1902), undated (Box 1)
  - Class day book, 1902; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1902 55th reunion book, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Class record book, undated (Box 2)
  - Clippings from Vassarion, 1902 (Box 1)
  - "Ethical Instruction in Elementary Schools, undated (Box 1)
  - Folder of door notes, undated; [3 folders] (Box 1)
  - Illustration for 1902 Vassarion by Caroline (Stoddard) Korell, undated (Box 1)
  - Notice - 1902 at 1901's Tree Ceremonies, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Proofs of Vassarion, undated; [8 folders] (Box 2)
  - Reunion song sheet music and 55th reunion materials, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Script for "1902 Dramatic Syndicate: Princess Ping Pong,", undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1903, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - "The 1903 Evening Herald', undated (Box 1)
  - 1903 50th reunion bulletin, 1953 (Box 1)
  - 1903's 50th Reunion (letters to E.T. Reed), 1953; [7 folders] (Box 2)
  - 1903's Song booklet, [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Booklet of photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Class day book, 1903; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class day exercises, 1903 (Box 1)
  - Class day songs and reunion materials, undated (Box 1)
  - "Class of 1903: A 1903 sampler,", 1960 Oct 2 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1903 bank materials, undated; [2 folders] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1903 reunion pictures, undated (Box 1)
  - Letters referring to Class of 1903 bulletin, undated; [3 folders] (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Officers' bulletin, undated (Box 1)
  - "Pride and Prejudice (a play" by Margaret Hudson, undated; [3 folders] (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Record of gift to the class of 1903 to the Department of Zoology, undated (Box 1)
  - "Report of 'Our Sixtieth' VC Class of 1903,", 1963 (Box 2)
  - "A Report to 1903 on the Fine Fifty-Fifth at VC,", 1958 (Box 2)
- Class of 1904, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - 1904 bookplate, undated (Box 2)
  - 1904 class seal, undated (Box 2)
  - 1904 minutes and report, undated (Box 2)
  - 1904's guest room, undated (Box 2)
  - 50th and 55th reunion bulletins, "Come Across 1904,", 1954, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Class day book, 1904; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Class of 1904 - Letters to Beth Adams, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1904 miscellaneous playbills and scripts, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1904 newspaper clippings, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1904 Programs and songbooks, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1904 Reunion bulletin, 1930 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1904 reunion invitation notice, 1935; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Class poems - "The Complete Works of 1904, Periodically Compiled by 1905,", undated; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class poems - "The Complete Works of 1904, Periodically Compiled by 1905,", undated; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Class songs, undated; [3 copies] (Box 2)
  - Class Treasurer's notebook (Kahn, Adeline), undated (Box 2)
  - "Columbia,", undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence to Alice Carson Bench, undated (Box 2)
  - "In Memoriam of Alice Lovett Lewis 1904,", undated (Box 2)
  - [Notebook of citations?], undated (Box 2)
  - Official copies of Reunion bulletins, undated (Box 2)
  - Papers on Herbert E. Mills Library fund, undated (Box 2)
  - Printed ephemera, undated; [3 folders] (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 2)
  - Report of the 5th year reunion, 1909 (Box 2)
  - Ruth Adams 1904 - [Notes on Engagement?], undated (Box 2)
  - Vassar 1904 Reunion Bulletin, 1914 Jun; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - "Who's Who in America,", undated (Box 2)
- Class of 1905, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - 1905 bulletin, undated (Box 1)
  - "1905 Flash News from the 75th Front,", undated (Box 1)
  - 1905 gavel, undated (Box 1)
  - Class Book, 1905 (Box 2)
  - Class box 1905 Mary Taber, undated (Box 2)
  - Class day book, 1905; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1905 - Miscellaneous, undated; [10 folders] (Box 2)
  - Class of 1905 First annual bulletin, 1906 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1905 pictures, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1905 stationary, undated (Box 1)
  - Class songbook, 1905 (Box 1)
  - Class songs, 1905 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence to Helen Kenyon, undated (Box 1)
  - Harnete Winslow Manuscript, undated (Box 2)
  - Newspaper articles - Commencement, 1905 (Box 2)
  - Obituary and Memorial Service: Mary Field Taber (VC 1905), undated (Box 2)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 2)
  - Reunion news, undated (Box 1)
  - Reunion photographs, undated; [2 folders] (Box 2)
  - "The story of Anne Ward - Vassar's first blind student,", undated (Box 1)
  - Vassar 1905 Class bulletins, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
- Class of 1906, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - 1906 Class material belonging to Marion Paine Walkley, undated (Box 1)
  - 1906 Treasurer's record, undated (Box 1)
  - Class day book, 1906; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - "Class of 1906 Song and other verses: second series Elsie M. Rushmore,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class songs, 1906; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - E. Buffington materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Ella Frances Harris (VC 1906) - Personal papers, undated (Box 1)
  - Ella Frances Harris photograph, undated (Box 1)
  - Ella Harris (VC 1906) - certificate of appreciation from the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1947; [rolled] (Box 2)
  - Ella Harris (VC 1906) - certificate, "Medaille de Guerre," Union des Femmes de France, Croix Rouge Francaise, 1919 Jul 9; [rolled, with mailing tube] (Box 2)
  - Ella Harris (VC 1906) - certificate, "Medaille de la Reconnaissance Francaise,", 1920 Aug 17; [rolled] (Box 2)
  - Ella Harris (VC 1906) - Plaque, undated (Box 2)
  - "Hope for the Hungry or a Corner in Pie,", undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Vassar pocket handbook, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
- Class of 1907, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - Class day book, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1907 5th reunion record, 1912 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1907 correspondence between Ms. Plum and Emily Pierson, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1907 stationary, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1907 Tree songs, undated (Box 1)
  - Class songs, 1907; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Commencement book, schedule, a drawing, undated (Box 1)
  - "Esthlon ekon metedos - 50th reunion bulletin,", 1957 (Box 2)
  - "Log Book of the Good Ship 'Vassar',", undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Newspaper articles, undated (Box 1)
  - Owl print, 50th reunion book, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Photographs of children of Alpha (Gabriel) Lewis 1907, undated (Box 1)
  - Poughkeepsie Daily Eagle article - "Simplicity the Rule in 1907's Class Day,", 1907 Jun 12 (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - reunion songs, undated (Box 2)
  - The Unsuspected Isle libretto, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Vassar pocket handbook, undated (Box 2)
  - VC Class of 1907 Second Bulletin, 1909 Jun (Box 2)
  - "What the Wise Old Owl Prophesies for 1907,", undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Wooden hammer, undated (Box 2)
- Class of 1908, [1 cubic foot (3 boxes)]
  - "1908 Reunion Gossip,", undated (Box 3)
  - 43rd annual catalogue of VC, undated (Box 1)
  - 50th reunion Class of 1908, 1958; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Angell, Lois (VC 1908) materials, undated; [2 folders] (Box 2)
  - Class day book, 1908; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Class day book, 1908 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1908 Christmas cards, undated (Box 3)
  - Class of 1908 Fundraising materials, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1908 Letters to H.M. Hequembourg, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1908 newspaper articles, undated (Box 3)
  - Class of 1908 observatory materials, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1908 schedules, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1908 secretary book, undated (Box 3)
  - Class reunion materials, undated; [2 folders] (Box 2)
  - Class sash, undated; [2 sashes] (Box 3)
  - Class songbook, undated; [2 copies] (Box 3)
  - Class songs, undated (Box 1)
  - Class supper, 1908 Jun 10; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Copy of The New Testament, undated (Box 3)
  - de Lima, Agnes (VC 1908) materials, undated (Box 2)
  - "The Gassarian 1908,", undated (Box 3)
  - "Invitation to 1908 Class Day Exercises, prob. belonging to Jinnet Christine Lielland,", undated (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 2)
  - Paper flower garland, undated (Box 2)
  - Printed ephemera, undated; [4 folders] (Box 2)
  - Program for "You Never Can Tell" - reunion, undated (Box 1)
  - VC "The Easter Music" pamphlet, 1908 Apr 19 (Box 2)
- Class of 1909, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "The Art of Following the Nazarene,", undated (Box 1)
  - Card from Freeman, Margery Fulton, undated (Box 1)
  - Class day book, 1909; [4 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1909 etchings, undated (Box 1)
  - Class songs, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - "Constitution of the Class of 1909, undated; [2 volumes] (Box 1)
  - "The Eaglet,", 1956 (Box 1)
  - "Fables in Slams" booklet (shaped like a cabbage), undated; [4 copies] (Box 1)
  - Founder's Day Book, 1909 (Box 1)
  - "The Gassarion,", 1908; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - "Last of the Waughties,", undated (Box 1)
  - Reunion materials and bills, undated; [2 folders] (Box 1)
- Class of 1910, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - 1910 class records, undated (Box 2)
  - Academic booklet, 1908 Oct 31 (Box 2)
  - Class bulletin, handwritten, undated (Box 1)
  - Class day book, undated (Box 1)
  - Class day books and commencement materials, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1910 Alumnae information, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1910 booklet, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1910 bulletins, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1910 Commencement articles, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1910 Guest book (Box 1)
  - Class of 1910 key, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1910 memorials, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1910 minutes, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1910 pictures of Ruth Harding and her classmates, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1910 reunion materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1910 Sarah Babson fund, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1910 Scrapbook, undated (Volume)
  - Class songs, undated; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - "Education and Child Care Institute in Germany" - about K. Taylor's work 1949, undated (Box 2)
  - "Education and Child Care Institute in Germany" - about K. Taylor's work 1950, undated (Box 2)
  - Negatives of Ruth Harding photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 2)
  - Reunion news, 1960; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Sheet music - "Stevenson's Requiem,", undated (Box 1)
  - VC 1910 Bulletin booklet, 1950 (Box 1)
- Class of 1911, [1.2 cubic feet (4 boxes)]
  - 50th anniversary materials, 1961 (Box 2)
  - Academic booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - Academic booklet, undated; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Bookplates designed by Julia (Lovejoy) Cuniberti (VC 1911), circa 1911; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - "Can'tbeburyed Tales,", undated (Box 2)
  - Class bulletin materials, undated (Box 2)
  - Class day book, 1911; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Class meeting notes, undated; [3 books] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1911 club materials and correspondence and ephemera, undated; [2 folders] (Box 2)
  - Class of 1911 commencement materials, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1911 funds, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1911 minutes, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1911 newspaper articles, undated; [3 folders] (Box 2)
  - Class of 1911 pictures, undated; [2 folders] (Box 2)
  - Class of 1911 reunion fan, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1911 Reunion materials, undated; [2 folders] (Box 2)
  - Class of 1911 reunion photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1911 Senior Parlor Guest Book, undated (Box 4)
  - Class photo and newspaper, undated (Box 2)
  - Class songs, 1911; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Directory of the Class of 1911 VC, undated; [4 copies] (Box 1)
  - Newspaper articles on Commencement from Poughkeepsie Daily Eagle, undated (Box 2)
  - Record book Class of 1911, undated (Box 3)
  - "Seniors' Own Journal,", undated; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Statistics for Class of 1911 record book (alphabetized), undated; [7 folders] (Box 3)
  - Twenty-sixth class bulletin, 1911-1937 (Box 2)
  - VC 100th anniversary materials, undated; [2 folders] (Box 2)
  - VC Class plaque, undated (Box 2)
- Class 1912, [2 cubic feet (6 boxes)]
  - 25th reunion program, 1937 (Box 2)
  - Class day book, undated; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Class of 1912 mailings and reports, 1918-1987; [2 folders] (Box 3)
  - Class of 1912 Miscellaneous correspondence, undated (Box 3)
  - Class of 1912 necrologies, undated (Box 3)
  - Class of 1912 Newsletter editors files, 1928-1936; [3 folders] (Box 3)
  - Class of 1912 Recording of 55th reunion, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1912 reunion newsletter, 1928-1930 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1912 reunion newsletter, 1931-1935 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1912 reunion newsletter, 1935, 1939; [3 folders] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1912 reunion newsletter, 1936-1944 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1912 reunion newsletter, 1945-1949 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1912 reunion newsletter, 1947 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1912 reunion newsletter, 1950-1959 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1912 reunion newsletter, 1960-1967 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1912 reunion newsletter, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1912 scrapbook - Part 1, undated (Box 4)
  - Class of 1912 scrapbook - Part 2, undated (Box 5)
  - Class of 1912 t-shirt, undated (Box 6)
  - Class records by month (in yellow box), undated (Box 6)
  - Constitution of the Class of 1912, undated (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 2)
  - Photographs 70th reunion, 1982; (g. Elizabeth Westbrook) (Box 2)
  - Printed ephemera, undated; [2 folders] (Box 2)
  - Report of Twenty-Fifth Reunion Class of 1912, 1937 Jun 4; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Report of Twenty-Fifth Reunion Class of 1912, 1937 Jun 4; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Reunion and AAVC materials, 1959-1988 (Box 3)
  - Reunion scrapbook, 1982 (Box 3)
  - "To Vassar Today... 50th Reunion,", 1962; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - VC 1912 Songbook, undated; [2 folders] (Box 2)
  - Westbrook, Elizabeth Botney (VC 1912) correspondence and photographs, 1957-1989 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1912 Guest book (Box 3)
- Class of 1913, [1 cubic foot (3 boxes)]
  - 20th reunion materials (collected by M. Jewell McVey), 1933 (Box 3)
  - 25th reunion film, 1938 (Box 1)
  - "Alice in Freshmanland,", undated (Box 3)
  - Class day book, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1913 Alumnae info, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1913 commencement and class materials (Box 3)
  - Class of 1913 Guest book (Box 2)
  - Class of 1913 reunion data, undated (Box 3)
  - Class songbook, 1913 (Box 2)
  - Class songs, 1913; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Diploma from Mount Holyoke College - Ethel Barbara Dietrich, undated (Box 3)
  - Gassarion, 1913-1914; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Letters and sympathy notes: to Elizabeth B. Mylod (VC 1913), undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Letters, undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 3)
  - Mount Holyoke Alumnae Quarterly, 1963 Winter (Box 3)
  - Newspaper articles concerning Amabel Scharff Roberts (VC 1913), undated (Box 3)
  - "Order of the Delta Gamma Rose of Delta Gamma Fraternity" to Ethel Barbara Dietrich, undated (Box 2)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 2)
  - Printed ephemera, undated; [2 folders] (Box 3)
  - "The Random" Vassar 1913, undated; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Record of Class of 1913 25th reunion, 1938; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Round Robin letters, 1914-1940; [2 folders] (Box 1)
  - The 1913 Arcade - "Bend to the Oars,", undated (Box 3)
  - VC 1913 reunion booklet, undated (Box 2)
  - VC Laundry List, undated (Box 2)
  - Washburn, Ruth W. (VC 1913) - medal given by city of LeHavre for work with children under sponsorship of the American Red Cross, 1919 Mar 15 (Box 1)
- Class of 1914, [1.2 cubic feet (4 boxes)]
  - 1914 class minutes, undated; [2 folders and 1 book] (Box 4)
  - "The 1914 Class Register,", undated (Box 3)
  - Cards with class names, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1914 class songs, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1914 negatives and photographs, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1914 programs and other pubs, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1914 Scrapbook, Vol. 1, 1964 (Volume)
  - Class of 1914 Scrapbook, Vol. 2, 1964 (Volume)
  - Class of 1914 Scrapbook, Vol. 3, 1964 (Volume)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 2)
  - Commencement scrapbook, undated (Box 1)
  - Gassarion to 1913 from 1914, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 2)
  - Tape recording of "Astronaut to Vega" by Julia Cooley Altrocchi (VC 1914), undated (Box 1)
  - Vassar pamphlet "Memorabilia,", undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1915, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - 1915 class minutes, undated (Box 1)
  - Class day book, 1915 Jun 8 (Box 1)
  - Class gavel, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1915 Guest book (Box 2)
  - Class of 1915 miscellaneous alumnae materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1915 miscellaneous photographs and letters, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1915 newspaper articles, undated (Box 1)
  - Commencement and Baccalaureate services and hall plays and choir program, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence to Irene (Ringwood) Arnold, undated (Box 1)
  - Essay on Doris L. Crockett, undated (Box 1)
  - "Impressions of the 75th' [reunion]" by Ivaa (Appleyard) Maginnis, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Katherine Wells' college materials and etc., undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs from 50th reunion, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Play and exhibition and class and Founder's day books, undated (Box 2)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 2)
  - "Remains of box buried beneath tree of 1915,", undated (Box 1)
  - Senior Parlor book, undated (Box 1)
  - Sheet music - "D'Accord Marching Song, Class of 1915, Vassar College," words and music by Adele M. Beattys (VC 1915) (Oversize Box 1)
  - Song by Emma Lester Seely, undated (Box 1)
  - Transcript of talk given at 1915 reunion dinner - "How Not to be an Onion,", 1958 Jun 13 (Box 1)
- Class of 1916, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - 1916 class minutes, undated (Box 2)
  - 1916 tribute, 1916 Sep - 1917 Oct (Box 2)
  - "Alumnae News Letter" report of AAVC Council meeting, undated (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of the class of 1916, undated (Box 1)
  - Class day book, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1916 Guest book (Box 2)
  - Class of 1916 tribute, 1916 Sep (Box 1)
  - Class reunion materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Class songs, undated (Box 1)
  - Class songs, 1916 (Box 2)
  - "Graduates of 1916" reunion - Poughkeepsie Journal, undated (Box 1)
  - "Members of 1916 Present on June 10th, Alumnae Day,", undated (Box 1)
  - "Sine Qua Non" - full score, undated (Box 1)
  - "The Speedometer,", undated (Box 1)
  - "The Vassar Primer,", undated (Box 1)
  - The Vassarion, 1916 (Box 1)
- Class of 1917, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 1917 class minutes, undated (Box 1)
  - 1917 songbook, undated (Box 1)
  - Highlights on Reunion booklet, undated; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Photographs of Theodora Bailey (VC 1917), undated (Box 1)